# **BRANDON MAXWELL**

## Interior Designer

(931) 644-0750 | Denver, CO. | branmaxwell12@gmail.com

## **PROFILE**

Interior Designer actively looking for my next opportunity in the design industry. I am proud to have a unique range of design experience that spans across five years and includes sectors such as corporate design-build, mixed-use multifamily, and flagship retail.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## STORE DESIGNER

Trek Bicycle Co.

OCT 2022 - SEPT 2023 | Remote (CO)

- Designed and developed a series of greenfield bike shops across North America, including a flagship location. Test fit through FFE.
- Introduced a custom new bike display to Trek retail; constructed from the company's recycled cardboard bike boxes in-store.
- Established a Revit model for Trek Waterloo HQ (205k sq.ft.) while simultaneously leading the first ever Trek Culture event in CO.

#### INTERIOR DESIGNER

Shears Adkins Rockmore Architects (SAR+)

AUG 2021 - OCT 2022 | Denver, CO

- Digitally formatted multimedia presentations using InDesign to assist clients in visualizing the architectural interior experience.
- Joined company teams to advance the firm in sustainability and culture while also further developing my own knowledge and skillset.
- Worked on small teams to produce multiple full-scale comprehensive designs for ground-up multifamily and mixed-use developments.

## **TECHNICAL DESIGNER**

HLW, Contract - Aerotek

JUN 2021 - JUL 2021 | Remote (NY)

- Independently created and developed over 100 design options over a duration of two months satisfying a time-sensitive client request.
- Established personal relationships with team members and completed all project work in a fully remote environment.

#### INTERIOR DESIGNER I

Unispace

OCT 2018 - JULY 2020 | New York, NY

- Leveraged different technical design programs to create custom design packages, construction sets, & 3D renderings for award winning design-build projects.
- Completed multiple projects from beginning conceptual phases through final punch lists while engaging consistently and reliably with the client on all fronts.
- Gained significant understanding of fast-paced work styles surrounding tight deadlines and small teams.

#### I TECHNICAL DESIGNER - Unispace, Contract

DEC 2020 - FEB 2021 | Remote (NY)

- As a returning employee I was able to onboard quickly and execute project-specific work that enabled the team to complete
  the deliverable ahead of schedule for the client.
- Efficiently modeled core and shell components for a shared cloud Revit model that was linked and used by a series of teams across North America and Europe.

## INTERIOR DESIGN INTERN

Eric Cohler Design

MAY 2018 - AUG 2018 | New York, NY

- Developed and articulated design solutions for luxury high-end projects & clients.
- Expanded, built, and maintained manufacturer and showroom relationships.
- Contributed to technical CD sets used to complete projects on time and within budget.

## PROFICIENCIES & SKILLS

Adobe Suite Revit
InDesign Enscape
Photoshop Sketchup

Bluebeam PC & Mac Google Suite 3D Modeling & Rendering Abstract Thinking Conceptual Development Technical Design Space Planning Leadership Oriented Organized
Problem Solving
Decision Making

#### **EDUCATION**

#### Bachelor of Science in Interior Architecture, CIDA

University of Tennessee at Chattanooga

- Student Member of ASID, IIDA, CSI, & USGBC. Interior Design Alliance (IDA) Resources Chair Member (2 YRS.)

#### RECOGNITIONS

**2022 Finalist - Justworks**SBID International Design Awards

**2021 Winner - Justworks** *IFMA NYC Awards of Excellence* 

**2021 Finalist - Justworks** NYCxDesign - Interior Design